https://atutor.ca/disclosure-privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Search
Toggle Navigation
Exam Prep ACTGREKaplanLSATLSATMaxMagooshMCATPrepScholarSATTEFLFor Students iTalkiOnline CoursesOnline Jobs for StudentsScholarshipsStudent AccessoriesStudent ElectronicsFor Tutors Free DownloadsTutor AccessoriesTutor ElectronicsLesson PlanningOnline TutoringPoject-Based LearningReading ComprehensionTeaching Kids to CodeTeaching with LEGOHomeschoolingPlannersSTEM / STEAM Education
Disclosure & Privacy PolicyAffiliate DisclosureATutor is a participant of different affiliates programs, and it is important for you to know, that some articles have affiliate links to generate revenue. We partner with some educational companies and are also part of the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program. If you click on an affiliate link and make a purchase, we will receive a small percentage of the revenue from the sale. However, this does not influence our editorial content.Please note that we only partner with companies and promote products and services that we believe in and trust.If you have any concerns regarding this, please contact us at info@atutor.ca.Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy has been compiled to serve better those concerned with how their’ Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person or to identify an individual in context.Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect, or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information by our website.Do we use ‘cookies’?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, enabling us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction to offer better site experiences and tools in the future.We use cookies to understand and save user’s preferences for future visits and to memorize the users who have unlocked access to premium content. If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled. It will affect the user’s experience, and some of our services will not function properly.Third-Party DisclosureWe do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third-party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We, therefore, have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us.About AtutorWe provide expert tutoring advice and provide posts that help students and tutors for better performances.Digital Teacher PlannerRecent Posts Tools and Apps for a Good Classroom Library Organization Best Teacher Easel for Classroom and Homeschool Use The 7 Best Classroom Rugs Teacher Will Love Is Italki Language Exchange Free and How Does it Work? What to Talk About on iTalki – Fun Ideas and SuggestionsCategoriesExam PrepACTGREKaplanLSATLSATMaxMagooshMCATPrepScholarSATTEFLFor StudentsiTalkiOnline CoursesOnline Jobs for StudentsScholarshipsStudent AccessoriesStudent ElectronicsFor TutorsLesson PlanningOnline TutoringPoject-Based LearningReading ComprehensionTeaching Kids to CodeTeaching with LEGOTutor AccessoriesTutor ElectronicsFree DownloadsHomeschoolingPlannersSTEM / STEAM EducationFollow us on Pinterest Contact usName *FirstLastEmail *Comment or Message *PhoneSubmitDisclosureCopyright © 2020
English
English German Portuguese Spanish
